-- 1. To get the list of customers in the database

-- 2. To get the list of orders in the database

-- 3. To get the list of regions in the database

-- 4. To get the list of orders for customer 1631

-- 5. To get the list of customers for the region BA, CH, MU, PU

-- 6. To get the list of orders for the year 2005

-- 7. To get the list of invoices for the year 2005 and for the customer 961

-- 8. To get the list of customers whose name begins with T

-- 9. To get the list of invoices either for the customer 1631 or for the month
-- March 2005

-- 10. To get the total number of customers in the database

-- 11. To get the total number of orders for the customer 1631 for the year 2006

-- 12. To get the total order value of the database

-- 13. To get the total sales value of the database for the customer 961

-- 14. To get the total outstanding amount of the database

-- 15. To get the total number of customers for each region [RegionCode, CustomerCount]

-- Top 3 regions with highest customer count

-- 16. To get the total number of orders for each customer id [CustomerId, OrderCount]

-- 17. To get the total sales value for each customer id [CustomerId, SalesValue]

-- 18. To get the total sales value for each customer in the year 2005

-- 19. To get the list of orders with its customer information
-- OrderId, OrderDate, CustomerId, CustomerName, RegionCode

-- 20. List of all invoices with their order information 
-- (InvoiceId, InvoiceDate, InvoiceTotal, OrderId, OrderDate)

-- 21. List of all invoices with their payment information
-- (InvoiceId, InvoiceDate, InvoiceTotal, PaidAmount, OutstandingAmount)

-- 22. List of all the orders for the year 2006 with their customer information
-- (OrderId, OrderDate, CustomerId, CustName, RegionCode)

-- 23. Item with or without order information
-- (ItemNo, LstPrice, MarketingFactor, Rate, Qty, Total)

-- 24. Customers with or without order information
-- (CustomerId, CustName, RegionCode, OrderId, OrderDate)

-- 25. Customer information with their invoice and payment information
-- (CustomerId, CustName, RegionCode, InvoiceId, InvoiceTotal, PaidAmount, OutstandingAmount)

-- 26. Customer information with their orders, with or without invoice and payment information
-- (CustomerId, CustName, RegionCode, OrderId, OrderDate, 
-- InvoiceId, InvoiceTotal, PaidAmount, OutstandingAmount)

-- 27. Orders with its item information
-- (OrderId, OrderDate, ItemNo, ListPrice, MarketingFactor, Rate, Qty, Total)

-- 28. Total number of orders for each region
-- (RegionCode, OrderCount)

-- 29. The total invoice value for each region in the database
-- (RegionCode, InvoiceValue)

-- 30. Total order value for each customer
-- (CustomerId, CustName, OrderValue)

-- 31. Total order value, invoice value and collections value for each customer
-- in the database
-- CustomerId, CustomerName, OrderValue, InvoiceValue, CollectionsValue


-- 32. Monthly sales report for the year 2006
-- MonthName, InvoiceValue

-- 33. Yearly Sales report for the customer 1631
-- Year InvoiceValue

-- 34. Region with the highest CollectionsValue
-- RegionCode, CollectionsValue

-- 35. To get the list of orders for the customer PRS using subquery

-- 36. Total number of orders in the database for each customer using subquery

-- 37. Customer with their sales value and collections value using subquery

-- 38. Orders for the customers belonging to the reigon 'BA' using subquery


-- 39. To check the list of items which do not have an order - using PREDICATE (EXISTS 
--		ItemNo, ListPrice, MarketingFactor

-- 40. Order Total for each region in the database using joins
